Guide to the Records of the Study of the Aspirations of Youth in a Developing Society (The Trinidad Study) RISM.RG.5
New York University Archives
- Series III: Questionnaires, 1957-1961
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Questionnaires: PK, 1957-1961 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Questionnaires: PL 18, 1957-1961 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Questionnaires: PM, 1957-1961 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Questionnaires: PRCB, 1957-1961 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Questionnaires: PT, 1957-1961 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Questionnaires: SJC, 1957-1961 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Questionnaires: SMC, 1957-1961 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Questionnaires: SMC, 1957-1961 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Questionnaires: Unidentified, 1957-1961 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Questionnaires: Unidentified, 1957-1961 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Series IV: Results
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Race Relations, 1957-1961 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Race Relations, 1957-1961 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Race Relations, 1957-1961 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Results, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Results: Achievement Data, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Results: Coding System, 1957-1961 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Results: Factor Analysis, 1957-1961 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Results: Ingroup-Outgroup Attitudes, 1957-1961 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Results: Tables, 1957-1961 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Series V: Statistical Data
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Statistical data, 1957-1961 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Statistical Data, 1957-1961 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Statistical Data, 1957-1961 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Statistical Data: Duplicate Tables, 1957-1961 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Statistical Data: GJ Naparima Teacher Training College, 1957-1961 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Statistical Data: Open End, 1957-1961 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Statistical Data: Proud Accomplishment, 1957-1961 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Statistical Data: Tables, 1957-1961 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Statistical Data: Tables by School, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Statistical Data: Trinidad and Tobago Tables, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Statistical Data: Trinidad and Tobago Tables, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - RISM: Trinidad Study: Statistical Data; [x Choice to 39 Race School], 1957-1961 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Series VI: 2017 Accretion (Box Shared University Archives Accessions 005, Folder 1-7)
  - Correspondence: Vera Rubin, 1957-1976
  - Notes and Working Papers, 1957
  - Publication Correspondence and Inquiry, 1966-1969
  - Survey - Completed (Human Subject Data), 1957